# **Cooper Featherstone**

2510 NW Turner Dr, Bentonville, AR, 72712 \* (310) 947-9988 \* cooperfeatherstone13@gmail.com

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Adaptable high school student (3.6 GPA) with 2 years of work experience and proven knowledge of web design, programming, and application development. Aiming to leverage my abilities to successfully fill the role at your company. Frequently praised as efficient by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

## **EDUCATION**

## BENTONVILLE HIGH SCHOOL

## Bentonville, AR

High School Diploma (Expected graduation May 2020)

- **GPA:** 3.6
- Relevant Coursework: Ignite IT Solutions professional studies, AP Computer Science, AP Statistics

## NORTHWEST ARKANSAS COMMUNITY COLLEGE

## Bentonville, AR

- **GPA:** 3.5
- Relevant Coursework: Intro to Programming Logic, Intro to Computer Information

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### CODE NINJAS, Bentonville, AR

Code Sensei, Mar 2019 - Present

- Teach Kids to Code
- Help the Kids When they get Stuck
- Write Performance Reviews for the Kids
- Train Myself
- Clean the Dojo

## WALMART, Bentonville, AR

Intern, Oct 2018 - May 2019

- Member of the International Mobile App Development Team
- Worked with ReactJS
- Worked With Redux
- Created UI/UX for Web Apps
- Monthly Presentations

## BELLA VISTA COUNTRY CLUB, Bella Vista, AR

Golf Cart Manager, Mar 2018 - Nov 2018

- Golf Cart Operations
- High Level of Customer Service
- Wash and Dry Golf Carts
- Enforce Golf Course Etiquette
- Custodial Services

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS / EXTRACURRICULAR

- Programming Experience: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, React, and C++
- Music: Piano, Ukulele, and Guitar
- Boy Scouts
- Volunteer on a Weekly Basis at Local Food Pantry
- Coding Club